(Janine:)Did it have six breasts?
I'm sorry, I'm a feminist. Heh.
I don't notice things like...
(Howard:)...how many breasts a robot has.
(Sheldon:)Well, hello.
(Leonard:)What are you doing here?
- Actually, I came to speak to Mrs. Davis.
- And I'm a little busy right now.
(Sheldon:)But I came to file a complaint. Somebody
has made me feel uncomfortable...
(Sheldon:)...in the workplace by using language
of an inappropriate and sexual nature.
- And who is that?
- You, you dirty birdy.
(Sheldon:)I thought about the things
you said yesterday...
(Sheldon:)...and I realized I'm deeply offended.
(Sheldon:)Now, be a dear and get me
one of those complaint forms.
(Janine:)That's it. All of you, in my office now.
(Sheldon:)Thanks to you, I know better
than to ask if you're menstruating.
Based on your behavior, I don't have to.
(Sheldon:)It has been pointed out to me that
some of the things I said to you...